import { QuizSetTypes } from "@/types/adda/quiz";

export const QUIZES: QuizSetTypes[] = [
  {
    _id: "1",
    category: "Music",
    type: [
      {
        artists: "Taylor Swift",
        _id: "11",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "111",
            question:
              "Taylor Swift started her music career mainly in which genre",
            options: ["Rock", "Pop", "Country", "Jazz"],
            answer: "Country",
          },
          {
            _id: "112",
            question:
              "Which Taylor Swift album is known for storytelling songs like ‚ÄúLove Story‚Äù",
            options: ["Reputation", "Fearless", "1989", "Midnights"],
            answer: "Fearless",
          },
          {
            _id: "113",
            question: "What does Taylor Swift love to include in her songs",
            options: [
              " Math formulas",
              "Personal stories",
              "Science facts",
              " Sports rules",
            ],
            answer: "Personal stories",
          },
          {
            _id: "114",
            question: "Taylor Swift is famous for writing most of her‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Dance steps",
              "Song lyrics",
              "Concert lights",
              "Costumes",
            ],
            answer: "Song lyrics",
          },
          {
            _id: "115",
            question:
              "What animal is often linked with Taylor Swift‚Äôs fan culture",
            options: ["Lion", "Snake", "Horse", "Panda"],
            answer: "Snake",
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        artists: " K-POP Artists",
        _id: "12",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "121",
            question: " What does K-Pop stand for",
            options: [
              "Kids Pop",
              "Korean Popular Music",
              " Karaoke Pop",
              "Kingdom Pop",
            ],
            answer: "Korean Popular Music",
          },
          {
            _id: "122",
            question: " Which country did K-Pop originate from‚Äù",
            options: ["Japan", "China", "South Korea", "Thailand"],
            answer: "South Korea",
          },
          {
            _id: "123",
            question: " K-Pop groups are famous for which combination",
            options: [
              "Singing + Dancing + Fashion",
              "Only singing",
              "Only rap",
              "Only acting",
            ],
            answer: "Singing + Dancing + Fashion",
          },
          {
            _id: "124",
            question: "BTS fans are called",
            options: ["Stars", "Beats", "Army", "Lights"],
            answer: "Army",
          },
          {
            _id: "125",
            question: "BLACKPINK has how many members",
            options: ["4", "3", "7", "5"],
            answer: "4",
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        artists: "Billie Eilish",
        _id: "13",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "131",
            question: "Billie Eilish became famous at a very young age",
            options: ["True", "False"],
            answer: "True",
          },
          {
            _id: "132",
            question: "Which song made Billie Eilish globally famous",
            options: ["Bad Guy", "Hello", "Roar", "Perfect"],
            answer: "Bad Guy",
          },
          {
            _id: "133",
            question: "Billie Eilish is known for which style",
            options: [
              "Loud classical music",
              "Opera singing",
              "Soft, whisper-style singing",
              "Folk music",
            ],
            answer: "Soft, whisper-style singing",
          },
          {
            _id: "134",
            question:
              "Billie often wears oversized clothes because she believes in‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Fashion rules",
              "Hiding talent",
              "Matching colors",
              "Comfort and self-expression",
            ],
            answer: "Comfort and self-expression",
          },
          {
            _id: "135",
            question: "Who helps Billie Eilish create most of her music",
            options: [
              "Her teacher",
              "A big band",
              "Her brother Finneas",
              "Her fans",
            ],
            answer: "Her brother Finneas",
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        artists: "Kendrick Lamar",
        _id: "14",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "141",
            question: "Kendrick Lamar is famous for which special skill?",
            options: [
              "Only dancing",
              "Deep storytelling and meaningful lyrics",
              "Playing violin",
              "Making movie music",
            ],
            answer: "Deep storytelling and meaningful lyrics",
          },
          {
            _id: "142",
            question:
              "Kendrick Lamar often talks about which topics in his music?",
            options: [
              "Real life, society, and emotions",
              "Cartoons",
              "Fairy tales",
              "Science experiments",
            ],
            answer: "Real life, society, and emotions",
          },
          {
            _id: "143",
            question: "Kendrick Lamar won a Pulitzer Prize for‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Acting",
              "Music lyrics and storytelling",
              "Fashion",
              "Sports",
            ],
            answer: "Music lyrics and storytelling",
          },
          {
            _id: "144",
            question:
              "Which Kendrick Lamar song is often used to talk about self-belief?",
            options: ["Baby Shark", "Perfect", "Roar", "HUMBLE"],
            answer: "HUMBLE",
          },
          {
            _id: "145",
            question: "Kendrick Lamar believes rap can be a form of‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Noise",
              "Storytelling and poetry",
              "Fighting",
              "Magic tricks",
            ],
            answer: "Storytelling and poetry",
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        artists: "Travis Scott üåå ",
        _id: "15",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "151",
            question:
              "Travis Scott is known for creating which type of music experience?",
            options: [
              "Calm bedtime music",
              "Classical orchestra",
              "Folk musi",
              "High-energy, space-like sound",
            ],
            answer: "High-energy, space-like sound",
          },
          {
            _id: "152",
            question: "Travis Scott concerts are famous for being‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Very energetic and visual ",
              "Silent",
              "Only sitting",
              "Very slow",
            ],
            answer: "Very energetic and visual ",
          },
          {
            _id: "153",
            question: "Travis Scott often uses what in his music?",
            options: [
              "Nature sounds",
              "Auto-tune and beats",
              "School bells",
              "Piano lessons",
            ],
            answer: "Auto-tune and beats",
          },
          {
            _id: "154",
            question: "Travis Scott‚Äôs music style is best described as‚Ä¶",
            options: [
              "Story-based only",
              "Opera lyrics",
              "Trap / modern hip-hop",
              "Jazz",
            ],
            answer: "Trap / modern hip-hop",
          },
          {
            _id: "155",
            question: "What makes Travis Scott different?",
            options: [
              "Fashion + music + visuals together",
              "Only lyric",
              "Only dance",
              "Only instruments",
            ],
            answer: "Snake",
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        artists: "Other Hip-Hop Artists üåç üéµ",
        _id: "16",
        questions: [
          {
            _id: "161",
            question: "Who is known as one of the first hip-hop pioneers?",
            options: [
              "Elvis Presley",
              "Taylor Swift",
              "Mozart",
              "Grandmaster Flash",
            ],
            answer: "Grandmaster Flash",
          },
          {
            _id: "162",
            question: "Which artist talks about confidence and self-belief?",
            options: ["Nicki Minaj", "Beethoven", "Adele", "Coldplay"],
            answer: "Nicki Minaj",
          },
          {
            _id: "163",
            question: "Who is known for smooth flow and storytelling?",
            options: [" J. Cole", "Shakira", "Ed Sheeran", "Bruno Mars"],
            answer: " J. Cole",
          },
          {
            _id: "164",
            question: "Which artist mixes hip-hop with fashion and business?",
            options: [
              "Selena Gomez",
              "Ariana Grande",
              "Justin Bieber",
              "Kanye West",
            ],
            answer: "Kanye West",
          },
          {
            _id: "165",
            question: "Hip-hop culture includes which elements?",
            options: [
              "Only singing",
              "Only instruments",
              "Rap, DJing, dance, graffiti",
              "Only movies",
            ],
            answer: "Rap, DJing, dance, graffiti",
          },
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
];
